////////////////////
// TODO LIST
//

* At the moment, messages reporting that some watched file has been modified are not shown while the "make" thread is running. This is done in order to avoid printf interleaving. A solution would be to delay the printing of these messages until the end of the execution of the make "thread". Another solution is to implement a separate thread responsible of the output of all other threads.

* Implement the InternalPreamble feature. In this mode, the preamble is automatically extracted from the main .tex file and there is no need to create a separate preamble file

* Add the following options:

 --psviewer={gsview|path to a .ps viewer}

 --pdfviewer={gsview|path to a .pdf viewer}

 --dviviewer="c:\long path\yap.exe"
	to overwrite the default viewer associated with the corresponding files.

* new values for the option -afterjob: for instance dvips2pdf.
